Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Writings, 1901-2009; 445627
  - Television: The People Speak - Viewer Reactions, Dec 2009, undated; cuid15758; 445994 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States - Correspondence, Jul 2006-Aug 2006; cuid15759; 446013 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States: Development Proposals (Independent Production Fund), May 2006; cuid15760; 446017 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States: Letters of Interest, 1996-2001, undated; cuid15761; 446019 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Television: A People's History of the United States: Treatments (12 episodes), undated; cuid15762; 446021 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Treatments: "Stop-Off at Ludlow" or "The Train to Trinadad" or "A Western Story" (working titles for "Purgatory River"), undated; cuid15763; 446027 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Series IV: Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1964-2008; 446033
  This series documents many of Howard Zinn's appearances and speaking engagements including lectures, speeches, panel participation, Congressional hearings, radio broadcasts, trial testimony and awards ceremonies. Arranged chronologically by the date of each event, materials may include correspondence, flyers and advertisements, press, contracts/agreements, notes and a few speech transcripts. In some cases, there is only a letter requesting his participation, annotated with the word "No".
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements (includes letter from Abbie Hoffman), 1964-1965; cuid15764; 446037 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1966; cuid15765; 446039 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1967; cuid15766; 446040 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1968; cuid15767; 446041 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1969; cuid15768; 446044 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1970; cuid15769; 446045 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1971-1972; cuid15770; 446046 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1973-1975; cuid15771; 446047 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1976-1977; cuid15772; 446048 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1978-1979; cuid15773; 446050 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1980; cuid15774; 446051 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1981; cuid15775; 446052 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1982; cuid15776; 446055 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements (includes Zinn testimony at Congressional Hearings on Defense Spending and letter from Ron Dellums), 1982; cuid15777; 446056 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1983; cuid15778; 446058 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1984; cuid15779; 446059 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1985; cuid15780; 446060 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1986; cuid15781; 446062 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1987; cuid15782; 446063 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1988; cuid15783; 446065 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1989; cuid15784; 446066 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1990; cuid15785; 446067 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jan 1991-Apr 1991; cuid15786; 446069 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, May 1991-Dec 1991; cuid15787; 446071 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jan 1992-Sep 1992; cuid15788; 446072 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Oct 1992; cuid15789; 446074 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Nov 1992-Dec 1992; cuid15790; 446083 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1993; cuid15791; 446084 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jan 1994-Jun 1994; cuid15792; 446085 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, Jul 1994-Dec 1994; cuid15793; 446086 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements (includes letter from John Conyers Jr.), 1995; cuid15794; 446087 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1996; cuid15795; 446088 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1997; cuid15796; 446089 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1998; cuid15797; 446090 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 1999; cuid15798; 446091 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2000; cuid15799; 446092 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2001; cuid15800; 446093 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2002; cuid15801; 446094 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2003; cuid15802; 446095 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2004; cuid15803; 446096 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2005; cuid15804; 446097 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Appearances / Speaking Engagements, 2006-2008; cuid15805; 446098 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Series V: Boston University, 1960-2003; 446099
  The first Boston University (BU) subseries focuses on Howard Zinn's teaching career including course syllabi, a few lecture transcripts, a number of his annual appointment forms and student evaluations of his teaching for the years 1969 through 1983. There are many examples of student work – papers, projects, journals and independent study – and a good deal of associated materials. The student journals not only provide a glimpse into the conduct of Zinn's classes and the materials he used, but also reveal reactions of the individual students.
  The second, and much larger subseries, documents many crises and controversies that occurred during Zinn's time at BU including suppression of academic freedom and civil liberties, censorship of campus press, attempts to build and strengthen the AAUP and other unions on campus, tenure and salary grievances, strikes and demonstrations, issues surrounding various University trustees and many examples of the rancor between Zinn and John Silber, former BU president. Some of the conflicts continue even after Zinn's retirement, including his active opposition to Silber's gubernatorial candidacy in 1990. It should be noted that material concerning specific controversies may be found in multiple folders. An event might, for example, appear in a general controversies folder, in a folder focused on the Committee to Save Boston University, in a folder addressing AAUP activities and in a folder titled with the name of the particular issue.
  - Subseries V:A: Teaching and Student Material, 1964-2003; 446100
    - Boston University Faculty Committee on Social Issues: Areas of Interest, 1966-1967; cuid15806; 446101 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Course Syllabi: "Introduction to Political Theory", 1968-1987; cuid15807; 446102 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Course Syllabi: "Law and Justice in America", 1970-1987; cuid15808; 446103 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Course Syllabi: Marxism Seminar, "Marxism and Anarchism", 1968-1984; cuid15809; 446104 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Course Syllabi: "Politics and History", 1969, 1979-1988; cuid15810; 446105 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Course Syllabi: Various, 1969, 1974-1988, 2003, undated; cuid15811; 446106 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Letters of Appreciation, 1977-1987; cuid15812; 446107 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Office Memoranda, 1978, 1986, undated; cuid15813; 446108 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Point, A Guide for Students and Faculty in College Two, 1973; cuid15814; 446109 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1969-1977; cuid15815; 446110 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1979; cuid15816; 446111 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1980; cuid15817; 446112 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1981; cuid15818; 446113 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, 1985-1987; cuid15819; 446114 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn, undated; cuid15820; 446115 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College, 1980; cuid15821; 446116 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Spring), 1981; cuid15822; 446117 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Fall), 1981; cuid15823; 446118 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Spring), 1982; cuid15824; 446119 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Fall), 1982; cuid15825; 446120 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Spring), 1983; cuid15826; 446121 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Student Evaluations of Zinn - Metropolitan College (Fall), 1983; cuid15827; 446122 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Annual Appointment Forms, 1976-1981; cuid15828; 446123 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Lecture Transcripts: "Wealth and Law" Lecture One and Two, undated; cuid15829; 446124 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Zinn Sabbatical, 1977-1978; cuid15830; 446125 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Zinn Student Letters, 1974-1982, undated; cuid15831; 446126 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Zinn Student Work: Correspondence (alienated), 1964, 1975, undated; cuid15832; 446127 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Zinn Student Work: Independent Study, 1981; cuid15833; 446128 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Zinn Student Work: Independent Study, 1982; cuid15834; 446129 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Zinn Student Work: Independent Study, [1982], undated; cuid15835; 446130 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1982; cuid15836; 446131 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1983; cuid15837; 446132 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1985-1986; cuid15838; 446134 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1987; cuid15839; 446135 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, 1988; cuid15840; 446136 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Zinn Student Work: Journals, undated; cuid15841; 446137 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1968-1975; cuid15842; 446138 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1976; cuid15843; 446139 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1979-1980; cuid15844; 446140 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1981; cuid15845; 446141 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, 1982, 1984; cuid15846; 446142 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Zinn Student Work: Papers, undated; cuid15847; 446143 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects (includes letter from Senator Harry F. Byrd), 1972-1978; cuid15848; 446144 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects, 1981-1985, undated; cuid15849; 446145 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1969; cuid15850; 446146 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1972-1973; cuid15851; 446147 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (I), 1974; cuid15852; 446148 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (II), 1974; cuid15853; 446149 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (includes print/artist's proof "Squeaky Fromme..."), 1975-1977; cuid15854; 446150 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1978; cuid15855; 446316 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1979; cuid15856; 446317 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1980; cuid15857; 446318 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1981; cuid15858; 446319 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1982; cuid15859; 446320 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1983, 1984; cuid15860; 446321 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1985; cuid15861; 446322 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (I), 1986; cuid15862; 446323 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material (II), 1986; cuid15863; 446324 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, 1987; cuid15864; 446325 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects - Associated Material, undated; cuid15865; 446326 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects/Papers (Housing and Tenant Issues), 1968-1972; cuid15866; 446327 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects/Papers (Housing and Tenant Issues), 1982; cuid15867; 446328 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Zinn Student Work: Projects/Papers (Housing and Tenant Issues), undated; cuid15868; 446329 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Student Work: "Struggle to Survive: A History of the Exposure's Rebirth and the Graphics and Exploits of Jeff Smith", [1982]; cuid15869; 446330 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Student Work: Various Items, 1988, undated; cuid15870; 446331 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Subseries V:B: Boston University Controversy, 1962-2002; 446238
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5), 1979-1980, undated; cuid15871; 446239 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Legal Proceedings, 1979-1980, undated; cuid15872; 446337 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): "Materials"; "Documents and Clippings", 1976-1980, undated; cuid15873; 446338 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Outdoor Class Attendees, 1979; cuid15874; 446340 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support (groups), 1979-1980; cuid15875; 446341 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support (individuals), 1979-1980; cuid15876; 446342 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support (Luria petitions), 1979; cuid15877; 446343 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Academic Freedom and the Boston University 5 (BU5): Support - Various Flyers, Lists, Notes and Other Related Material, 1979-1980, undated; cuid15878; 446350 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1974-1975; cuid15879; 446352 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1976-1977; cuid15880; 446353 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (I), 1978-1979; cuid15881; 446354 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (II), 1978-1979; cuid15882; 446355 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (III), 1978-1979; cuid15883; 446357 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1979-1980; cuid15884; 446358 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1980; cuid15885; 446359 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1980-1981, undated; cuid15886; 446360 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (I), 1981; cuid15887; 446361 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials (II), 1981; cuid15888; 446362 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Materials, 1983-1985, undated; cuid15889; 446364 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Anti-War (Vietnam), 1968-1973; cuid15890; 446365 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Anti-War (Vietnam): Police Action March 27, 1972, cuid15891; 446366 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Banner Hanging Dispute: Abramowitz, Yosef I. et al. v. Trustees of Boston University, 1986; cuid15892; 446369 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Bias against Zinn, [1974]-1980, undated; cuid15893; 446370 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1965-1970; cuid15894; 446373 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1972-1979; cuid15895; 446374 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1980-1981; cuid15896; 446375 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1982; cuid15897; 446377 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1983; cuid15898; 446378 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1985; cuid15899; 446379 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1986-1989; cuid15900; 446381 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1990-1996; cuid15901; 446383 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Boston University Controversy, 1991-2002, undated; cuid15902; 446384 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Boston University Labor Council (BULC), 1979-1980, undated; cuid15903; 446392 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Budget / Financial Issues, 1976-1979, undated; cuid15904; 446393 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Budget / Financial Issues, 1976-1986, undated; cuid15905; 446394 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Building and Grounds Workers (SEIU, Local 254), 1977-1979; cuid15906; 446395 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Building and Grounds Workers (SEIU, Local 254): Strike, 1978; cuid15907; 446396 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Building and Grounds Workers (SEIU, Local 254): Strike - Press, 1978; cuid15908; 446397 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure, 1977-1984, undated; cuid15909; 446398 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure - Articles from the bu exposure and Daily Free Press, 1977-1983; cuid15910; 446399 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure - the bu exposure Collective v. John Silber, et al., 1978-1983; cuid15911; 446400 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Campus Media: the bu exposure - the bu exposure Collective v. John Silber, et al. - Silber Deposition, 1982; cuid15912; 446401 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Campus Media: WBUR, 1977-1978, 1986; cuid15913; 446402 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1974-1987; cuid15914; 446404 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Chronology of Daily Free Press Items, [1985]; cuid15915; 446405 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Civil Liberties - Clippings, 1972-1986; cuid15916; 446406 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts (CLUM) Inquiry and Report, 1979; cuid15917; 446407 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts (CLUM) Inquiry and Report - Related Material, 1976-1980, undated; cuid15918; 446408 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1973-1980, undated; cuid15919; 446409 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1974-1980; cuid15920; 446410 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1979-1980; cuid15921; 446411 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1979-1980, undated; cuid15922; 446412 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Committee to Save Boston University, 1980, undated; cuid15923; 446414 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Committee to Save Boston University: Lists and Related Materials, 1979, undated; cuid15924; 446415 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Committee to Save Boston University: State Senator Gerard D'Amico, 1980; cuid15925; 446416 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Department of Political Science, 1974-1975; cuid15926; 446417 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Diamandopoulos, Peter, 1997-1999; cuid15927; 446418 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Draft Registration and Financial Aid, 1983; cuid15928; 446419 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Draft Registration and Financial Aid: Doe, John and Paul Poe v. Trustees of BU and Silber (I), 1983; cuid15929; 446420 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Draft Registration and Financial Aid: Doe, John and Paul Poe v. Trustees of BU and Silber (II), 1983; cuid15930; 446421 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Council Opposition to Duarte Honorary Degree (and Silber response), 1986; cuid15931; 446422 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Tenure, Appointments, 1969-1987, undated; cuid15932; 446423 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Tenure, Appointments: Bottome, Edgar, 1970, 1972; cuid15933; 446424 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Tenure, Appointments: Giroux, Henry, 1982-1983; cuid15934; 446425 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lists, Various, 1980-1988, undated; cuid15935; 446426 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Marcuse, Herbert (substitute for Zinn), 1974; cuid15936; 446427 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - "Mismanagement and Corruption", 1978-1990; cuid15937; 446428 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1977; cuid15938; 446429 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1978; cuid15939; 446430 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1979; cuid15940; 446431 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Newspapers: the bu exposure, 1980, 1983; cuid15941; 446432 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, 1972, 1977, 1978; cuid15942; 446433 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, Jan 1979-Feb 1979; cuid15943; 446434 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, Mar 1979-Apr 1979; cuid15944; 446435 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Newspapers: The Daily Free Press, Oct 1979-Apr 1981; cuid15945; 446436 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Nursing School Closure, 1987; cuid15946; 446437 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Photograph (Howard Zinn, Frances Fox Piven, Murray Levin), 1977; cuid15947; 446815 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - "Pursuing Excellence at Boston University" by Frances Piven, Murray Levin and Howard Zinn, 1975; cuid15948; 446438 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Redmont, Bernard S., 1985-1986; cuid15949; 446439 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - "Report of the Boston University Faculty Council on Academic Freedom", 1996; cuid15950; 446440 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1972; cuid15951; 446441 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1972-1974, undated; cuid15952; 446450 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1973; cuid15953; 446451 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, 1976, 1980, 1984; cuid15954; 446452 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) and Military Recruitment, undated; cuid15955; 446453 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Silber, John: Arson Accusation against Howard Zinn, 1972, 1979-1980; cuid15956; 446454 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1972-1979; cuid15957; 446455 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1972-1990, undated; cuid15958; 446456 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1980-1987; cuid15959; 446457 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Silber, John: Articles, Various, 1993-1995, undated; cuid15960; 446458 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Silber, John: Faculty Call for Removal of Silber, 1979-1980; cuid15961; 446484 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Silber, John: Faculty Call for Removal of Silber - Outside Support (alumni), 1979-1980; cuid15962; 446485 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Silber, John: Faculty Call for Removal of Silber - Outside Support (includes letter from Henry Steele Commager), 1979; cuid15963; 446486 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Silber, John: Letters, Letters to Editor re: Silber, 1976-1979, 1989-1999, undated; cuid15964; 446487 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race, 1989-1990; cuid15965; 446488 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber", 1990; cuid15966; 446489 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Silber, John: Massachusetts Gubernatorial Race - "Factbook on John Silber" - General, 1990; cuid15967; 446490 (Box 25, Folder 7)